



### **About Me**

I'm a psychologist with experience in a number of clinical settings. I've worked with a large number of clients with different backgrounds and presenting problems. Prioritizing empathy and helping clients process emotions is a key part of my practice. CBT and EFT are modalities I commonly utilize due to their versatility and explanatory scope.



## Contact



+90 530 747 2416



ansar.yavuz@yahoo.com



@psikologensardeniz



### References

• Arthur Cardona, PsyD. - Midwestern State University

arthur.cardona@msutexas.edu

- · Uzm. Psk. Dr. Tahsin Pektoylan Aritmi Osmangazi Hastanesi
- +90 224 270 0500 / 1016



### ্র্টি Skills

- Rapport-building
- Therapy (e.g. CBT, EFT)
- · Psychological testing (e.g. WAIS, WISC, CPT)
- Play therapy
- Adolescent therapy
- Report-writing
- Interdisciplinary collaboration

## At Languages

- English (Native)
- Turkish (Native)

# **Ensar Deniz**

# **Clinical Psychologist**



## **Education**

(2022 - 2024)

MIDWESTERN STATE UNIVERSITY Wichita Falls, Texas, USA

Clinical/Counselling Psychology -Master of Arts

(2018 - 2022)

**BURSA ULUDAG UNIVERSITY** 

Psychology - Bachelor of Science



# 🖶 Professional Experience

(2023 - 2024)

#### STUDENT CLINICIAN

Rose Street Mental Health Clinic

- · Provided psychological support and services to clients of various backgrounds and presenting problems (ADHD, MDD, SAD, ASD etc.)
- Worked collaboratively with supervisors and faculty to ensure quality care for clients
- · Administered testing to clients to assess psychological functioning and disorders (e.g. WISC, WAIS, CPT)

(2022 - 2023)

#### STUDENT CLINICIAN

Midwestern State University Psychology Clinic

- Developed and applied therapeutic skills by working with clients of various backgrounds and presenting problems
- · Received regular supervision from faculty on client improvement and therapeutic development



- · Continued training in **Cognitive-Behavioral Therapy**
- Psychotherapy training at The **Chicago School**
- · Clinical observations and Interview Techniques training Program
- Certified seminars on: Neuropsychological performance, psychological durability in children, how to control anxiety, living with a narcissistic partner, and secrets to a happy relationship
- Certificate of Honor Bursa **Uludag University**
- 1330 SAT score 93rd percentile
- Clinical internship in VR technologies in therapeutic processes - Sone Psikoloji



- Philosophy
- Theology
- Jiu Jitsu

# **Ensar Deniz**

# Clinical Psychologist



# Professional Experience

(2020 - 2022)

### **ENGLISH TEACHER/TUTOR**

Private practice

- Providing education and training to students of various ages in the English language
- Developed educational methods and strategies tailored to student needs and goals
- Held one-on-one and group classes focused on speaking, reading, writing, and listening

(2020 - 2022)

#### **ENGLISH TEACHER/TUTOR**

Serpil Kalin Yabancı Dil Kursu London Cafe & Speaking Club

- Administered testing to students to assess their linguistic skills
- Provided holistic education in the English language tailored to student goals